[ ZOMBIES SNARLING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Hmph .
COLUMBUS : Welcome to Zombieland .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Back for seconds ? After all this time ?
Well , what can I say , but thank you .
You have a lot of choices
when it comes to zombie entertainment ,
and we appreciate you picking us .
So you know how Eskimos
have a bunch of words for snow ?
[ COLUMBUS SPEAKING ON-SCREEN TEXT ]
The only reason we 've survived the last several years
is we 've gotten to know our bloodthirsty enemies
better than we know ourselves .
In the time since we last saw you ,
zombies have evolved ,
so we 've given them different names .
[ WOMAN SCREAMS ]
This lady here is getting chased
by the dumbest Z there is , what we call a Homer .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLS ]
In a world without YouTube ,
who isn 't entertained by a Homer ?
[ GROANING ]
D 'oh !
[ GRUNTING ]
Unfortunately , for every Homer ,
there 's a Hawking , as in Stephen .
Or maybe his slightly less accomplished sister , Beatrix ,
who 's still got some brains left to figure shit out .
Open , open !
[ ZOMBIE GROWLING ]
[ GLASS SQUEAKING ]
[ RASPY BREATHING ]
[ CRUNCHING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SOFT POP ]
[ SCANNER BEEPS ]
[ YELLS ]
Clever girl .
[ SCREAMS ]
Okay . Last one .
Whoa ! Whoa , whoa , whoa , what was that ?
Okay , all right . Well , this time ,
let 's play Name That Zombie .
Hello ?
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
- [ GROWLS ] - [ SCREAMS ]
The Ninja . Silent , deadly .
The first thing you hear is your own scream .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
You can imagine how thrilled we were to crack the zombie code .
But life is about more than just survival .
Ever since we were evicted from our normal lives ,
I 'd been searching for a place to put down roots .
My old pal Tallahassee has this saying , " Go big or go home . "
It 's not his signature phrase , but it did give me an idea .
Why not go big ...
and go home ?
[ METALLICA 'S " MASTER OF PUPPETS " PLAYING ]
♪ End of passion play ♪
♪ Crumbling away ♪
♪ I 'm your source of self-destruction ♪
♪ Veins that pump with fear ♪
♪ Sucking darkest clear ♪
♪ Leading on Your death 's construction ♪
♪ Taste me You will see ♪
♪ More is all you need ♪
♪ You 're dedicated to How I 'm killing you ♪
♪ Come crawling faster ♪
♪ Obey your master ♪
♪ Your life burns faster ♪
♪ Master Master of puppets ♪
♪ I 'm pulling your strings ♪
♪ Twisting your mind And smashing your dreams ♪
♪ Blinded by me You can 't see a thing ♪
♪ Just call my name ' Cause I 'll hear you scream ♪
♪ Master Master ♪
♪ Master of puppets I 'm pulling your strings ♪
♪ Twisting your mind and smashing your ... ♪
Hail to the motherfucking chief .
[ " HAIL TO THE CHIEF " PLAYING ]
COLUMBUS : There are worse places
to hang your hat .
[ SIGHS ] Casa Blanca .
Wait , why does he get to be president ?
I would have made a damn fine president .
Kissed a few hands , shook a few babies .
You would have brought a real dignity to the office .
- Thank you . - You don 't have what it takes .
- I 'll be president . - Heh !
And I nominate Little Rock as my VP .
So that means I get to be president
if you get killed by zombies .
That wasn 't what I was thinking
when I offered you the position , but yes .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
COLUMBUS : I have this rule :
Enjoy the little things .
Which is what we spent a lot of time doing
in those early days at the White House .
And it was a really special time ,
making a house our home .
[ BOTH CHUCKLING ]
♪ Happy birthday to ... ♪
Shooting up , not to . All right . Nice !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
COLUMBUS : Wichita and I fell into our own version of domestic bliss .
Well , not quite bliss , but domesticity to be sure .
Did Abe 's blindfold fall off again ?
No , it did not fall off . I took it off .
It 's so creepy . He stares at us all night .
That stare emancipated the slaves ,
and ended the Civil War .
We should be grateful he 's gawking at us .
Remember what happened the last time you took the blindfold off ?
You made me sleep on the Lincoln couch ?
Mm-hm .
[ PAPER TEARING ]
- Is that better ? - Much better .
- Good . - [ LAUGHS SOFTLY ]
TALLAHASSEE : I love you so much , baby .
You are so gorgeous .
We really need to find you someone .
That 's where you 're wrong .
Any romance left in me belongs to the Beast here .
Okay . Well , then we need to find someone for me .
Heh , heh , heh , shouldn 't be a problem ,
long as you 're open to dating zombies .
So you 're saying what ? I 'm never gonna find a boyfriend ,
or get married , have a family ?
We 're you family , so one out of three ain 't bad .
COLUMBUS : Little Rock had a strong desire to leave the nest .
And let 's just say Tallahassee
wasn 't the most understanding father figure .
Little Rock !
COLUMBUS : But for better or worse ,
we were a family .
And for the first time since the virus ,
we were living somewhere truly safe ,
making every day feel like ... Well , like Christmas morning .
Hello ? Ho-ho-ho !
Merry Christmas !
- Hey , Tal . - Santa .
What would you like for Christmas , little girl ? A pony ?
I 'd like you to stop calling me " little girl . "
Well , technically , you are little and you 're a girl .
I am not a little girl , but do you know what I would like ?
I don 't give a fuck what you 'd like .
COLUMBUS : Not to sound too sentimental ,
but those days at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue
may have been the best days of my life ,
and that 's counting pre-Z .
Wait a second .
Oh , my God . No .
A first-edition Tolkien , and you wrote in it .
There 's my name , marring this perfectly preserved paper .
Thank you . And yours too .
You didn 't stop . Thank you so much .
TALLAHASSEE : It 's a bit touching .
Hey , you know , I couldn 't find any wrapping paper ,
but don 't worry about it . Just tear it open .
It doesn 't matter . It 's only Taft .
He was our fattest president , so there 's a lot left over
if you need some wrapping paper .
Columbus , I didn 't get anything from you .
Just what I wanted . Another gun .
Oh , hey , well , not just any gun . A Colt .45 .
And not just any Colt .45 . The King 's .
- England ? Denmark ? Lichtenstein ? - There 's only one king .
Elvis Aaron fucking Presley , the greatest who ever lived .
The king of kings .
He gave this gun to Nixon when he visited the White House ,
and I give it to you , locked and loaded .
Yeah , he used to shoot that Colt in his backyard .
King 's palace , Memphis , Tennessee .
- I tell you about Graceland ? - Only a hundred times .
We 'll go there together someday .
Actually , I 'm gonna go shoot this right now .
I think I saw some Zs down by the reflecting pool .
- I 'll go with . - I 'll go by myself .
- It 's Christmas . - It 's not fucking Christmas .
It 's November 17th .
COLUMBUS : Little Rock was on the hunt , all right ,
for people her own age .
And the thing is , they were out there .
We just made it a point to keep our distance .
Which would suck if you were the one stuck in the nest .
God , this is really terrifying , but totally unrealistic .
Hm ...
Hey , she 'll be fine .
Wish she didn 't remind me so much of me .
Hey , come on . What 's wrong with you ?
[ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
Nothing .
All right . I wasn 't gonna do this now .
Okay . Look , you always say that , like , I play it too safe ,
and I know we 've been in , like , a bit of a rut lately .
So I thought , what better way to spice things up than to ...
Get married ?
Yeah , well , I was gonna say , " Get married ! " Yay !
- Is that the Hope diamond ? - I certainly hope it is .
I want you to be Miss Ohio . Or I guess Mrs. Ohio .
This is unfair . You know how I feel about this .
- What ? - We 've talked about this .
In my limited , but absurdly painful experience ,
married people only do one thing .
- What , fight ? We already do that . - Get divorced .
I don 't see us going that route .
I mean , where would we find the lawyers ?
- I don 't know what to say . - Well , don 't say anything . Yet .
- Okay ? This was my fault . - I put you on the spot .
Just think about it , and let me know whenever you 're ready .
Everything will work out exactly as it 's supposed to .
[ SIGHS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ COLUMBUS WHISTLING ]
Hey , Buttercup . What 's wrong ?
Get a little too much eggnog last night ?
- Bad news . - Bad news ?
Well , you know what cancels out bad news ? Good news .
Today is the day that Wichita says ...
Adios .
Hm ?
" Dear C and T , we feel like total shit about leaving .
Sorry , not good at notes . W and LR . "
Well , yeah . " Not good at notes "
is a pretty huge understatement .
He 's gonna take this Beast thing pretty hard .
Well , he should learn to not get so attached .
Never get attached . Remember ?
That was the problem with Columbus ,
he got too attached .
Well , with Tallahassee , it 's like
- he thinks he 's my dad . - Sure .
But you are lucky you don 't have a boyfriend .
Have you seen him use Q-tips ?
His bedtime routine took an hour .
- Stop . - What ? God , sorry .
- No , stop ! Stop ! - Oh !
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Namaste .
Hi .
COLUMBUS : Wichita leaving hit me like a shotgun blast .
So after weeks of feeling sorry for myself ,
I thought a little retail therapy
might help get her off my mind .
It 's not like I wanted to start ,
wedding planning or anything . I 'm not crazy .
Who wants to get married in winter ? Spring , sure .
- Though my hair and humidity ... - Oh , my God !
Man , I cannot listen to this shit anymore .
- My God , it 's been over a month . - Yeah , I 'm bereft .
Okay , I 'm giving you one more day to mope around ,
and then you gotta snap the fuck out of it .
This whole " finding a home " idea of yours has made us soft .
And by us , I mean you .
It 's high time that we nut up and hit the road again .
And by we , I mean me .
That 's where I belong .
On my own . Lone wolf .
- You 're welcome to tag along . - But when they come back ,
- we won 't be here . - They 're never coming back !
- [ GLASS SHATTERS ] - [ ZOMBIE GROANING ]
[ GUN COCKS ]
I got it .
No , no , no , no , no , no .
Okay . Uh ...
It was good . You shot your alcohol with your gun .
[ ZOMBIE GAGGING SOFTLY ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Not bad , huh ?
Hm , no . Not bad , but definitely no ZKOTY .
COLUMBUS : ZKOTY , that is " Zombie Kill of the Year . "
Like a junkie in search of a higher high ,
Tallahassee is no longer happy with Zombie Kill of the Week .
Which , if you 're keeping score ,
just went to Dave Sanderman of Riverside , Iowa .
You may wanna set down the Milk Duds for this one .
You dead , zombie !
[ GROANING ]
Whoo-whee , pig !
[ LAUGHING ]
COLUMBUS : Congratulations , Dave .
I never told you this before .
In fact , I never told anybody .
But I have Native American blood coursing through my veins .
- Like , right now ? - Yeah . Right now .
Blackfoot Indian to be exact . The freest men in history .
Mid-1800s , roamed the plains ,
no houses , no laws , no possessions ,
no chiefs to report to , no wives to listen to .
They listened ...
to the call of the buffalo .
[ SCOFFS ]
And they hunted those buffalo
by herding them off the cliff to their deaths .
- The great buffalo jump . - Whoa .
I don 't know why I never told anyone about my Blackfoot blood .
I guess it 's a sacred little secret .
Honestly , you 're the first paleface
I have genuinely trusted
because you 've always been there for me .
You care and you listen . You really listen ...
COLUMBUS : Unless you 're in a 4D theater ,
there is no way I can communicate
how bad Z-land smells ,
which is why I like candles so much .
Today , maybe a frosty gingerbread
or a Bahama breeze .
Mmm .
[ GLASS CLINKING ]
Whoa !
Oh , my God ! Please forgive me . It 's fake fur !
Oh , God . I 'm so sorry . I thought you were a ...
- You thought I was a zombie ? - Yeah . Of course .
Oh , my God , no . I don 't even eat meat .
I 'm a vegetarian . Vegan , actually . Heh .
- Sorry . Hi , I 'm Columbus . - Madison . Heh-heh .
- Oh , hi . Nice to meet you . - Nice to meet you .
All right . We 're hugging . So soon . Nice to meet you .
It 's nice to touch a human .
- TALLAHASSEE : Don 't mind me . - Oh , hello .
If I can have my body ? Hi , sorry .
This is Tallahassee . This is Madison .
- Madison , Tallahassee . - Is this your dad ?
For shit 's sake , slightly older , better-looking friend .
- Ha , ha , cute . - You live here ?
No , Paul Blart . I live in the freezer in Pinkberry , mm-hm .
It keeps the zombies out , though it is awfully chilly .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Do you ever consider turning it off ?
Couldn 't find the switch anywhere .
Just hoping the electricity would run out .
It 's amazing . As long as it rains , the dams give us power .
Apparently not brain power .
I feel like you 're being super judgy .
Like , I 'm getting a real anti-me vibe off of you .
- Are you ? - Oh , my God . There it was again .
- Yeah , I saw it . - And that 's hurtful , okay ?
I 'm , like , really good at surviving .
I carry a can of mace with me everywhere I go .
And I can run really , really , really , really fast .
Probably because I used to do hot yoga and SoulCycle .
Cardio ! Sorry , I do a lot of cardio too .
It 's actually my number one rule , which is so dorky .
But I have a list of rules for surviving Zombieland .
- Really ? - Yeah .
- So do I ! - You have rules
- for surviving Zombieland ? - Mine is just mostly
- stay in the freezer . - Oh .
[ GIGGLES ]
You know , we set up camp ,
like , down the road at the White House .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
The White House ? Oh , my God .
Would you wanna come hang out ?
- I would love that . - Cool .
Okay . How many rules do you have ?
- You wanna know about my rules ? - I wanna hear all of them .
- Well , number two is double tap . - Double tap .
- Double tap , yes . - Double tap you .
- You got me . I 'm murdered . - Ha-ha-ha .
COLUMBUS : Okay , yeah , I know what you 're thinking .
She 's absolutely not my type .
But after Wichita broke my heart ,
I was just excited to talk to somebody
who smelled like a candle , and not whiskey and gunpowder .
So Wichita and Little Rock left .
It was just us guys again . You know , bachelors .
This guy . You know , making a mess .
Which actually brings me to rule number 53 , Wet-Naps .
- Wow . - Yeah .
I can 't believe that you keep all this stuff in your head .
Heh , thank you .
- It 's amazing . - Thank you .
- You know , you 're really lucky . - What ?
That you found someone so smart to take care of you .
Most people your age , they get left all by themselves ,
and that can be so sad .
- Yeah . I am so lucky . - Oh !
[ CHUCKLES ]
Can we have a little summit in the Oval Office ?
Yeah , sure .
You guys , I can 't believe
we 're in the White House . This is soy random .
You got to broom this girl . You know why she 's still alive ?
Because zombies eat brains , and she ain 't got any !
All right ? It doesn 't matter
because I 'm hitting the road come sunup .
- MADISON : Columbus ? - Yes ?
Could you maybe give me a tour ?
Whoa , this is the Oval Office .
Why do they call it that ?
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
- You ready ? - You ready ?
- I 'm ready too . - I 'm ready .
- Great . - Too .
[ LAUGHS ]
- Let 's go . - He 's kind of funny .
Yeah , he 's great . Try not to speak to him .
Okay .
COLUMBUS : The main attraction .
Ta-da , the Lincoln bedroom .
Believe it or not , Lincoln never even slept here .
I didn 't actually want a tour , silly .
- What ? Oh . - Hi .
Hi .
Mm-mm , mm-mm .
- What 's the matter ? - I don 't know .
- Don 't you think that I 'm pretty ? - Yes , you 're very pretty .
You 're like , " Girl in Apartment 406 " pretty .
I just ... I feel kind of guilty .
Because of Jesus ?
[ WHISPERS ] I know ways around that .
- No , no . I ... Please . I can 't . - [ IN NORMAL VOICE ] Okay , look ,
I 've been alone in a freezer for years .
So either we 're doing this right now ,
or I am biting the bullet , and I am doing the old guy .
Okay .
God ! You 're so hot ! Oh my God !
- It 's the humidity . - MADISON : Oh , yes !
- [ MADISON MOANING ] - [ WALLS BANGING ]
Holy ...
Nutting up , definitely not shutting up .
- MADISON : Yeah ! - [ LOUD CRASHING IN THE DISTANCE ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- Aah ! Oh , shit ! - Oh ! Whoa !
Sorry , it 's Washington 's old flintlock .
It 's a gift to Eisenhower from the emperor of Japan .
Oh , touché .
- I heard a strange noise . - Yeah .
I 've been hearing some strange noises too .
Oh , yeah . That was us having sex .
Rule number one .
Yeah , maybe rule number 32 for her .
What ? Hey .
Okay . Ready ?
- Go ! - Okay , let 's go . Come on .
TALLAHASSEE : Oh , fuck . Shit .
- Honey , I 'm home . - Oh , my God , you 're back .
I mean , you 're back or whatever . That 's cool .
I 'm not staying . I came to get weapons .
At 1 : 00 in the morning ?
Yeah , after a month missing .
Little Rock 's gone .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
It was great . It felt so good to be on the move again .
We 've been having a really good time here too . Together .
We picked up someone new . Just a boy .
He 's a couple years older than Little Rock ,
and he 's from Berkeley .
- Berkeley ? - Mm-hm .
♪ Don 't worry about a thing ♪
- TALLAHASSEE : You said Berkeley ? - Yes .
TALLAHASSEE : Berke-fucking-ley ?
- ♪ ' Cause every little thing ♪ - WICHITA : He plays the guitar .
Shut the fuck up right now !
I know what you 're about to tell me .
She 's dating a musician !
Come on , don 't you think you 're , like , overreacting a little bit ?
Yeah . Yeah . No , I could be overreacting .
I 'm ... I 'm sorry . You 're right .
You go ahead .
And he 's a pacifist .
He has survived on a strict policy
of conflict avoidance , like Gandhi .
No !
Birkenstocks , sandals , wheatgrass !
Fucking basketballs !
[ TALLAHASSEE YELLS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
No , I really ... I have nothing against pacifists .
I just wanna beat the shit out of them .
♪ This is my message to you ♪
[ APPLAUDS ]
Wow , I mean ... You have a beautiful voice .
- Thank you very much . Thank you . - Yeah .
Hey , have you ever heard of this place , Graceland ?
Elvis was a fraud . He ripped off the black man .
Oh . I ... I don 't know . I 've just always wanted to go there .
Yeah , me too . Yeah .
- Graceland would be cool . - Yeah . Yeah , it would be .
WICHITA : I was adamant it was a dumb idea ,
so I did what I never do with her , I told her no .
You can guess what happened next .
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
[ PANTING ]
She left a note , and then she hit the road .
[ GIGGLES ]
Does anyone else get the irony in that ? Huh ?
I 'm so worried , you guys .
They 're traveling all that way ,
and all they have is a fucking guitar .
Yeah , with no intention of ever swinging it at anything .
You know , because he 's a hippie .
She 's supposed to be killing the dead ,
- not following them . - Oh , God .
There 's something going on out there .
- What ? - Berkeley told us
about this new kind of zombie
that 's stronger , and faster ,
and deadlier and better adapted to the hunt .
I 'm sorry , but that sounds totally made up .
If you want us to come with you , just ask us .
Honestly , I just came back for guns and ammunition .
Come on . Stop begging . We 'll do it .
You know , this is all your fault .
- Me ? - If you hadn 't pushed her away ...
Well , not exactly , no .
I didn 't just run from him .
She ran from you too .
What ?
You ... You mean well , but you 're ...
kind of overbearing .
Oh , right . I 'm overbearing ?
She 's not a kid anymore .
Yeah , she 's not a kid , but I don 't know ,
it sounds like she needs us .
Whatever . We 're gonna go get her .
We ride at dawn .
Once she 's safe , I 'm going my own way .
So no goodbye , just like ...
- Yeah , I 'm terrible at notes . - A lame note .
Yeah , I know . You mentioned that in the note .
Uh , I , uh ...
I might have overreacted a little bit .
I mean , the proposal kind of spooked me .
Mm-hm .
You know what I 'm trying to say .
Oh , God . I 'm sorry .
You know how hard it is for me to say that
because I hate women who are always apologizing
for things they have no reason to apologize for .
But in this particular instance , I actually am really sorry .
Well , thank you . That actually does mean a lot .
I don 't know . Maybe this could be like a ...
Like a turning point for us .
Yeah , maybe .
Columbus , you coming back to bed ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Wow .
Oh ... Oh , boy .
I mean , wow !
[ SCOFFS ] Glad we had this little talk . Real turning point .
Hi .
- Is that your sister ? - Oh , fuck .
[ SIGHS ]
You definitely don 't need any help .
- No , I 've got it . - Cool .
The Beast is back .
I cannot wait to get my hands behind the ...
What the fuck ?
No , no , no , no , no .
No way is that GD minivan even sniffing at Graceland ,
home to perhaps America 's finest automobile ,
Elvis ' 1955 Fleetwood Series 60 .
No . You know , it takes a real man to drive a pink Cadillac .
[ SIGHS ]
Might make that a rule of my own .
On second thought , fuck that ,
rules are for pussies . Nothing personal .
How could it not be ? That 's my thing .
Yeah , you 're right . It was personal .
Yeah . It 's gonna be okay .
COLUMBUS : Even Tallahassee knows
beggars can 't be choosers .
Vehicles with working batteries and parts
are way scarcer nowadays ,
thanks to years of neglect and decline .
Breakaway mirror .
We can 't be so picky anymore .
- Clear . - What ? Oh , okay .
- Booyah . - Okay .
Heh !
- This never happened . - COLUMBUS : I 'll get the door .
WICHITA : I got it . I 'm gonna lay in the back .
- Oh , catch . - Oh !
Shoot . Heh , I got it !
What in the butt ?
- Ah , shit . - What ?
- MADISON : Hi ! - Hi .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Are we dropping her off
at an animal shelter or something ?
She 's a human being .
We 're not gonna leave her here alone .
[ IMITATES MADISON ] We can 't just leave Columbus ' girlfriend .
Okay .
A minivan . Nice .
I 'm not gonna feel guilty .
You left me in the harshest way .
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] You recovered quickly .
- Well , thank you . - Can you help me ?
- I got it . - Okay .
- It 's just , like , heavy . - No problem .
- Thank you . - Go ahead , get in .
Okay . You are so nice .
Ah , Makkapitew , Askuwheteau , Sunukkuhkau ...
Is he having a seizure ?
I 'm trying out Blackfoot names ,
so full shushy or you go back in your mall fridge .
Okay .
Oh , I didn 't tell you . We met at the mall .
- Mm . - Yeah . I was living there .
Like Dawn of the Dead .
Last I checked , it 's the post-acropolis .
It was so sad when the acropolis struck .
Yeah , I know .
Madison , can you remind me , when we first met ,
did you point a gun at me and steal my car ?
No . When we first met ,
I told you you were really smart .
- Oh , yeah . - And then I slept with you .
That 's right . You did .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
MADISON : Road trip ! Here we go !
TALLAHASSEE : This is gonna be a long drive .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
I love the smell of gunpowder in the morning .
Eh , I 'm more of a patchouli oil guy myself .
You don 't ... You don 't have weed , do you ?
I 've always wanted to smoke way too much weed .
Do I look like the type of person
that would have weed on me ?
Oh , no . I w ... That ... I 'm sorry , that was ...
- Boom , yeah . - Ha ! Oh .
- Of course I do . Oh , I love weed . - You got me there .
- Look . I mean , look at me . - Yeah .
I wanted to say it 's really nice to have another woman around .
Yeah .
Like to talk about relationships .
- Recipes . - Rings .
Oh , my God .
- Oh , my God . - Oh , shit .
I know ! I found it in the bedside drawer .
I think it belonged to the first lady or ...
You know what ? I think you 're right .
It did belong to the first lady .
Well , I think it was given to the first lady ,
but she heartlessly rejected it .
What kind of idiot would turn down a ring like this ?
Maybe an idiot who didn 't wanna be weighed down .
Anchored . Chained to something immobile .
Hmm ...
- [ HORN HONKS ] - [ MADISON YELPS ]
[ BRAKES SCREECH ]
- Oh , shit . Are you okay ? - Oh , shoot !
Forgot the seatbelt rule .
So she knows the rules ?
Yeah , I told her just a few of them .
- Seventy-three . Are there more ? - Nope , that 's it .
- I gotta check this out . - You guys have spent
a lot of time together , huh ?
That 's sweet .
You 're cute together . I like it .
[ MOCKINGLY ] Oh !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
This looks promising .
He 's so flexible .
That 's what 's so great about him . He 's very bendy .
Ohio , whenever you 're done with that ...
What ? Yeah .
Ah !
COLUMBUS : What ? No . No , no , no .
No way . Nonstarter .
You know how I feel about clowns .
- No , not that . - What ?
- TALLAHASSEE : That . - COLUMBUS : Oh .
- Looks good . - Mm .
- MADISON : Can I see ? - Hm ?
Can I see ?
Yeah . Here you go . Yeah .
[ GASPS ]
- The old man is so tiny . - Can you see that ?
[ MADISON GIGGLES ]
What 's-his-name , you 're so tiny .
Now you 're not . Now you are .
Now you 're not . Now you are . Now you 're not .
Tiny . Big . Tiny !
- She is adorable . - She is . I 'm lucky .
Tiny . Big . Tiny .
[ CROWS CAWING ]
COLUMBUS : You 're overreacting , okay ?
Madison 's not a real thing .
It was just circumstance . It was a lack of options .
You could say the same thing about us .
- What ? - Circumstance , lack of options .
Really ? You really think that ?
Whereas you two seem like soul mates .
Destined to share deep thoughts .
Maybe you 're right , maybe we are soul mates .
Because she 's nice , all right ? And I 'm nice .
And you 're not . You 're mean .
- Whatever . I 'm not mean . - Yeah , you 're kind of mean .
Well , my sister is missing . She could be dead .
You 're screwing some Forever 21-year-old .
So if I wanna be mean , I 'll be mean .
I don 't have the right shoes .
Oh , you could borrow a pair of my strappy sandals .
- Really ? - Mm-hm .
Kidding . You ... She was ki ... You guys are all very sarcastic .
Yeah , they 're not nice people . Sorry . Just try to ignore them .
- Yeah . Yeah . Ignore us . - Please , God , ignore us .
Ah , see ? Mean .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
All right !
This is what I 'm talking about .
We 're finally gonna be riding in style .
I partied with 3 Doors Down in one of these . It was so ...
- [ CAR ALARM BLARING ] - COLUMBUS : Oh , shit .
[ GROANING ]
[ GROWLING ]
MADISON : What ?
[ ALARM SHUTS OFF ]
Man , we 're getting good at this .
- TALLAHASSEE : Columbus . - Tallahassee .
- The hood is 12 o 'clock . - Yes .
Trunk is 6 . You 're our eyes .
Hey , don 't worry , you guys .
They are much more afraid of us than we are of them .
God , that is not even remotely true .
- Well , what do I do ? - You know how cheerleaders
- form a pyramid ? - Yeah .
And the three on the bottom
- anchor the pyramid ? - Oh , yeah .
I don 't give a shit what you do , just stay out of my way .
Okay , 8 o 'clock . Eight o 'clock .
Did you say the front was 12 ? Oh , fuck me . Sorry . Two o 'clock .
Eleven ! Eleven ! Seven-thirty !
Six o 'clock . Six !
I 'll get 6 .
[ GROANS ]
Uh , shit . One-fifteen .
One-thirteen , 1 : 20 .
It 's moving that way .
Why is everyone shouting numbers ?
Eleven !
- MADISON : Twelve ! - Six !
COLUMBUS : Two o 'clock !
Eight .
- Six o 'clock . - Shit .
One o 'clock . Six-thirty .
Ten ! Eight !
[ GUN CLICKS ]
- Eight ! - Shit .
[ ROARING ]
Shit !
[ MADISON SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
- Narsty ! - Thank you .
You 're welcome .
One o 'clock ! Two-thirty .
Three ! One !
Okay . I 'll get 3 .
Right on time , Columbus .
[ BLOWS ]
One o 'clock ! Ten-thirty !
[ GROWLS ]
Eleven ! Eleven !
Actually , it 's a Homer .
Abort ! Abort 11 . Don 't waste a bullet .
- Hawking ! Hawking ! - What ? Oh , shit !
[ ROARS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
Yay !
[ GROWLS ]
- Aah , he 's trying to bite me ! - Ninja ! Ninja !
Oh , my God !
You saved me .
All right . Settle down .
[ GRUNTING ]
- Hey , Tal , 1 o 'clock . - Pardon me , Pop-Tart .
Not quite done yet .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
TALLAHASSEE : What the fuck ?
[ ROARS ]
Try to dodge me , motherfucker .
COLUMBUS : This was our first T-800 ,
named for the Terminator it-fucking-self .
Uh ...
- Tal ? - Yup ?
[ ZOMBIE GROANING ]
COLUMBUS : T-800s were a mutated strain of zombie ,
stronger , deadlier and harder to kill .
One plus one is still two , right ?
COLUMBUS : They were the apex predator , top of the food chain .
Single-minded and relentless like their namesake ,
once they locked on to a target ,
T-800s stopped at nothing to devour their prey .
What the ever-loving fuck ?
Ew .
COLUMBUS : Seeing that T-800 firsthand
was all the more worrisome
knowing that Little Rock was out there
with nothing but a hippie and a guitar .
♪ Like a rollin ' stone ♪
Okay . That song is amazing .
Did you write that ?
[ CHUCKLES ]
Wa ... Was that a dumb question ?
Sorry , I was like 11 when the zombies took over .
Not a dumb question .
I was laughing because you think
I 'd play some stupid cover song .
Of course I wrote it .
If you love that ,
then you 're really gonna love this .
But it 's a work in progress , so be gentle .
[ STRUMS GUITAR ]
♪ If I leave here tomorrow ♪
♪ Would you still remember me ? ♪
[ LYNYRD SKYNYRD PLAYING ] : ♪ I must be traveling Onward ... ♪
- A poem by Tallahassee . - Ah !
Traveling to Graceland In comfort and class
That Pontiac Trans Sport Can kiss my ass
- [ ALL LAUGH ] - [ EXCLAIMS ]
- Very good ! Very good . - Here we go , baby ! Woo-hoo !
Let 's go see the King and let 's go get Little Rock !
[ MADISON WHOOPS ]
[ TALLAHASSEE WHOOPS ]
♪ ' Cause I 'm as free ... ♪
- [ MADISON SCREAMS ] - [ TIRE HISSING ]
- Did ... Did we just get ... - Shorter ?
I say we take the clown car .
No , no , no . No ! That is a deal-breaker .
No fucking clowns !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
In moments of great dishonor such as this ,
ancient samurai warriors were required to commit seppuku ,
or ritual suicide by disembowelment .
MADISON : My mom had this car .
- WICHITA : So did mine . - COLUMBUS : So did mine .
[ MADISON GIGGLES ]
- [ KEY CLICKS ] - [ ENGINE STARTS ]
TALLAHASSEE : Fucking minivan .
MADISON : Back on the road , yay !
[ MADISON GIGGLES ]
I 've always wanted to start a business
where strangers drive strangers around in their car
- for money . - Mm .
MADISON : Let 's say you were really drunk and needed a ride home .
You 'd just get online
and hop right in with a stranger .
And they 'd take you anywhere you wanna go .
- Oh , yeah . Who then kills you . - Yeah . Ha , ha !
They 'd have gum or , like , lollipops .
That was what my parents taught me .
They were like , " If a stranger offers you candy or gum ,
get in their car . " Great idea .
MADISON : If they try to murder you ,
you can have a system so you can rate them .
If they try to murder you , like , " You get zero points . "
But if they don 't try to murder you , " You get five points . "
Madison , I think it is a very good idea .
That 's ... No , I cannot see that going wrong .
All I 'm saying is the taxi industry was very flawed .
[ BURPS ]
- Mm , oop ... - Are you okay ?
I think I 'm , like , hot . I 'm hot .
- Yeah ? - Mm-hm .
I 'm used to being in the freezer all the time .
- Get this off . - Yeah . Sure . That makes sense .
[ STOMACH RUMBLES , PASSES GAS , BURPS ]
[ HIGH-PITCHED VOICE ] I feel funny . My tongue ...
[ SLURRING ] My tongue ... My tongue ...
Boss ? You 're gonna wanna pull over .
[ YELLING INCOHERENTLY ]
- TALLAHASSEE : No . - Pull over .
We 're making good progress .
- Ugh ! - Pull over !
- Yeah . - Okay . Okay .
[ GROANING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROANS ]
- Oh . - Oh .
Chunkage .
Maybe she 'll pull through .
What ? You are the one who says " don 't take chances . "
[ RETCHING LOUDLY ]
So who wants do the honors ?
I mean , personally , I wouldn 't mind ,
but I don 't want you guys calling me selfish .
Hey , come on . She is a living , thinking being . Okay ?
She 's a living being .
Look , I know you guys are in love or whatever ,
but in two minutes , she 's gonna become a :
[ GROWLS , HISSES ]
A zombie , not a velociraptor . And it 's the right thing to do .
If you love something , you shoot it in the face
so it doesn 't become a flesh-eating monster .
I know .
TALLAHASSEE : She 's making a good point .
Maybe it 's time for you to be the Brave Little Toaster .
[ RETCHES , GROANING ]
COLUMBUS : They say when something bad happens ,
you have three choices :
Let it define you , destroy you , or strengthen you .
[ COCKS GUN ]
Time to teach Lennie about the rabbits .
[ RETCHES , GROANING ]
No ! Don 't come with me ! Don 't come with me !
COLUMBUS : Madison , Madison , please .
- Madison , please . Please , please . - Don 't hurt me !
- No , no , no ! - Wait . Listen to me !
- Please . Wait . - No , no , no !
- Madison , just wait . - I 'm a monster .
- I 'm a monster . - Please , please .
Listen . I realize we don 't know each other that well .
I mean , well , we do in the biblical sense , yes .
But I think you 're a really great person .
[ GROANS ]
Well , not now .
[ SCREAMING ]
I 'm sorry .
[ SHOTGUN FIRES TWICE ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Thanks .
Can we just , uh ...
I 'm so sorry .
All right . Just ... Come on , come on , let 's go .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
I 'm not gonna lie and say
that I 'm broken up about it , but , um ...
- I am sorry . - Yeah .
- She didn 't deserve that . - Thanks , man .
He 's right . That 's a terrible way to go , even for ...
- It 's ... . - Oh , come on . It 's Madison .
- You know that . - Madison !
You know that , okay ? Her name is Madison .
Or her name was Madison . And she was a real person , okay ?
She had , you know , complex feelings
and emotions and interests .
She liked dolphins and rainbows , you know ? And double rainbows .
- I 'm agreeing . It 's sad . - Okay .
That is obviously not what I wanted .
- What is it that you do want ? - I wanna find my sister .
Me too .
- Good . - Good .
- Good . Great . Awesome . - Great , in fact . Great .
This is gonna be a long drive .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
WICHITA : This is it .
Hey , little buddy , don 't be cruel to me
for waking you up , but we 're here .
Oh . Oh , my God .
Oh , my God .
[ LAUGHS ]
Every choice I 've ever made in my life
has been leading me to this moment right here ,
right now , 3764 Elvis Presley Boulevard .
I feel like a 1954 teenybopper .
And here comes ...
No .
No , no , no !
Hey , dude , if you need , like , a moment or ...
Oh , my God . No Graceland .
No Beast .
- No Little Rock . - TALLAHASSEE : No Little Rock ?
Am I not allowed
one cock-sucking duck-fucking little break in this world ?
You 're not the only one that 's upset .
Just ... Just drive . Drive , drive . Drive now !
Get away from here . Go !
COLUMBUS : Graceland was a pile of rubble ,
Little Rock was still missing ,
and we were unsure of our next move .
But sometimes , you just have to follow the signs .
Hm .
Well , when Z-land serves you lemons ...
Hey , Florida , 11 o 'clock .
What ?
- Hound Dog Hotel . - Oh , what a bunch of bull .
- Whoa , the Beast ! - Little Rock !
[ COCKS GUN ]
TALLAHASSEE : Damn . Wow ,
for a place that ain 't Graceland ,
it sure looks a hell of a lot like Graceland .
- Yeah , it does . - Here 's the idea .
We 'll split up . I 'll go this way .
No , no , no . I should talk to her .
I 'm her sister . I 'll talk to her first . You guys stay here .
Mm , sound .
- Huh . - Buh , buh , buh , buh .
- Little respect . - Why ? He 's dead probably .
Oh . Oh , for you . Okay .
- This is so degrading . - It 's not for me .
Yeah , I know .
Okay .
- Oh , yeah . - Smells like a wet dog died .
- That 's not ... Push it . - I am .
- Square peg , round hole . Stop . - Yeah , okay . Sorry .
Oh , my God . It 's uncanny .
This is incredible .
It 's a perfect fit . I feel like Cinderella at the ball .
Are you jealous that I have the same size shoe as Elvis ?
No . It 's not like those are Elvis ' actual shoes .
Sorry .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ LOUDLY ] ♪ Well , I never been to Spain ♪
[ PLAYING TUNE ON PIANO ]
Little Rock ?
♪ The ladies are insane ♪
♪ And they don 't have it easy ♪
♪ Well , I never been To heaven ... ♪
Ow !
[ GUN COCKS ]
- Start talking . - Ah , you first .
- Hi , my name 's Tallahassee . - Nevada .
- Which part ? - Nevada 's as close as you get .
Now , what are you doing in the Hound Dog ?
[ IMITATES ELVIS ] I got a thing for the King .
No , no , don 't shoot my friends .
- Anybody else in here with you ? - [ IN NORMAL VOICE ] No , just us .
We 're all civilized people . Let 's just put the guns down .
Why the hell are you wearing Elvis ' actual shoes ?
Comfort .
- You live here ? - Yeah .
So that car out front , the girl who was driving it , is she ...
Gone . She and that poser peace lover of hers ...
- Berkeley . - Berkeley .
... took off a few days ago .
And trust me , they shouldn 't have .
It 's not safe out there .
- Damn it . - Why didn 't they take the Beast ?
He said it was too " establishment . "
Oh , I will kill that little fart snack myself .
You 're lucky I didn 't do the same to you .
Seriously . You know how close I came to Murraying you ?
To what-ing him ?
Murraying him . You know , when you shoot someone
because you think they 're a zombie .
Apparently , that 's how Bill Murray died .
Wow , God , who 's Bill Murray ? I never ...
I don 't even know what that is .
Oh , the actor . That 's so sad .
I don 't read Variety . That 's sad .
Sorry if you knew him . If you didn 't , I 'm still sorry .
It 's sad when anybody dies . Sounds like an urban legend .
- It happened . - I doubt it . It 's weird . What ?
I 'll say this about Murray ,
if I ever find out who did him , I 'm gonna do him .
Me too . I 'll be ... You first , but me second .
WICHITA : Don 't listen to this guy .
He 's killed more celebrities than cocaine .
The girl that was here before ,
did she say where she was going ?
No , but that idiot Berkeley
wouldn 't shut up about it .
Babylon is a commune , safe haven ,
protected on all sides .
Completely pacifist . No guns or violence of any kind .
A lot of young people too , you know .
Generation Z living in peace and harmony .
- It sounds cool . - I know you had your heart set
on this Graceland , but this is mucho , mucho better .
[ GROWLING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
This is a very good replica of the King 's Jungle Room ,
where he recorded his last two albums .
From Elvis Presley Boulevard , Memphis , Tennessee and ...
And Moody Blue .
You know your Elvis .
Every lover of the King has a story .
What 's yours ?
My mama took me to see Elvis when I was a kid .
Something about him . Attitude , the music ...
The hips , the ass .
Well , I was 10 , but with Elvis ,
there is something for everyone .
Cut to later , I 'm in high school .
And my buddy Frankie Hammond says , uh :
" Do your Elvis . "
I said , " We 're in the library . It 's gonna be loud . "
He convinces me . He starts tapping his pencil ,
and I get up .
♪ You ain 't nothing But a hound dog ♪
♪ Crying all the time Bo , bo , doo-de-doo ♪
Everybody starts gathering around and clapping ,
and I jumped on a table . I finish off with a flourish .
♪ You ain 't never Caught a rabbit ♪
♪ You ain 't no friend of mine ♪
[ TAPS OUT DRUM BEATS ]
Yeah ! And the whole place , thunderous applause .
And up comes the cutest girl in the school ,
Robin Rogers , who never gave me the time of day before .
She plants a kiss on my cheek .
And for a moment , just one ,
I felt like the King .
I suddenly feel a little jealous of Robin Rogers .
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
You don 't say .
I don 't know about you
but I feel my temperature rising .
[ COUGHS ]
Mm .
This is Babylon .
Oh , like those ancient hanging gardens .
- Huh ? - Of Babylon .
No , no . It 's named for that cool David Gray song .
Man , I wish I 'd written that one .
No guns allowed is our one rule .
- That , and no group sex . - MAN : All right . Hand them over .
Here you go .
No guns . No guns . Just hugs .
Then welcome .
Come on , señorita . You 're gonna love this place .
It 's completely safe and entirely organic .
- LITTLE ROCK : This is so cool . - MAN : All right .
We 're gonna melt your guns here and give you a pendant .
- LITTLE ROCK : They melt it ? - BERKELEY : Yeah .
MAN : It 's a symbolic thing .
BERKELEY : Goodbye , violence .
Hello , peace .
MAN : Once we 're done ,
we 'll take you up to the rooftop .
I hope you like stairs .
MAN : That 's good .
- Thanks . - Welcome to Babylon .
Let me show you the way .
Aw , right on .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Hey , brother . What 's up ?
- Hi . - Yeah .
TALLAHASSEE [ IMITATING ELVIS ] : Wake up , my little blue suede baby .
It 's now or never . Ooh !
My friends say you 're sleeping like a tired pup .
[ CAR HORN BLOWS " DIXIE " ]
What the fuck ?
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
Shit .
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
Oh , no , no , no !
This is not happening !
This is not fucking happening !
Hey , motherfucker , that 's my ride !
Oh , my apologies , tiny Elvis .
Just didn 't expect anything to be parked in my driveway .
Your driveway ?
That 's right . My driveway .
Well , that 's funny . When I parked in it ,
no one told me to pull out .
[ SCOFFS ]
Well , actually , it 's my driveway .
Hey , Nevada .
But see , when I 'm in town , I use it .
Well , I 'm in town now , and I 'm using it .
Keep talking like this , and I can arrange
so neither of you ever uses my driveway again .
I don 't think they 're talking about the driveway .
No , I don 't think so .
- You happy now ? Good move . - Satisfied ? Good job .
- Does he remind you of ... ? - Yeah , it 's weird .
BOTH : I don 't like you at all .
It 's not weird , it 's creepy .
It 's like an un-funhouse mirror .
I think you double-parked or more perpendicular-parked .
- Hope we don 't get a ticket . - Whoa .
- Calm down . - I 'm just ragging you .
- What is going on here ? - What ?
- What do you mean , " what " ? - What ?
- Does he not remind you of ... ? - Hello , everyone .
Of ... Of what ?
- This is Albuquerque . - Howdy .
- I 'm Flagstaff . - Hey . I 'm Columbus .
Oh , great .
Uh , this is Tallahassee , Wichita ,
- and I guess you know Nevada . - Yes , I do .
Easy , cowboy .
So sorry about your ex-car .
I guess , as I like to say , expect the unexpected .
- It 's one of my commandments . - Oh .
- Commandments ? - Yeah . Sort of guidelines
for staying alive . I 've got loads of them .
- Hm , interesting . - Number one is teamwork .
Teamwork . That 's so great .
I spent a long time thinking about it .
I have rules , you know , which is , like , less biblical .
I love rules . Without rules , everything 's chaos .
- Thank you . - Columbus has quite a few rules .
- I do . - Awesome . Like what ?
- I don 't wanna toot my own horn . - Go on , toot .
- Let me toot for him . Uh ... - Thank you .
- Number one , cardio . - That 's right .
Cardio . Okay .
- What ? - I don 't mean to laugh .
It 's just that cardiovascular fitness is his number 29 ,
meaning he has 28 other commandments
that he finds more important ,
like , say , what 's one of your great ones ?
Number 12 . The world is your bathroom , meaning
you can whip it out wherever you want , and have at it .
Oh , just whip it out wherever you want !
That sounds a little uncouth .
The " whip it out " part 's for guys , obviously .
If you 're a woman , you can reveal it .
- Whichever . - I have beware of bathrooms .
Yeah , I 'm just generally careful around them .
But it 's not a competition .
- No , doesn 't have to be . - But number 18 is limber up .
- But that 's ... - That 's fine . I have warm up .
Again , not a competition , but commandment number 45
for me is , well , mind your manners .
Just because it 's the apocalypse
doesn 't mean you have to be rude .
Keep your hands to yourself , number 42 .
Do you have sunscreen ?
- Just shade . - Shade . Of course .
It 's free . It 's everywhere . Yeah . Number two , double tap .
I have number five , confirm your kill .
- Confirm your kill . - Avoid perishables .
- Do you have that ? - Sorry . Ziploc bags .
- Same thing , different word . - Yeah . Exactly .
I probably would shy away from the word " Ziploc "
because I try to avoid name brands .
Okay , great . So , what brought you guys back so soon ?
We was headed for the Rockies , but the goddamn Bolts ...
- Bolts ? - Yeah .
The zombies out on the plains .
They 're a lot tougher than what we 're used to .
I guess because of all the running and hunting .
So we call them Bolts , as in Usain .
As in pretty fucking athletic .
COLUMBUS : No , that makes total sense .
- We call them T-800s . - Terminator . Yes ! I love it .
COLUMBUS : Really ?
Yes . My favorite movie . Well , T2 .
Yeah , T2 is my second favorite movie .
- What 's number one ? - Uh , it 's Fantasia .
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALBUQUERQUE : Well , anyhow ,
the Bolts ' food sources are running low ,
so they 're pushing east , which is no bueno .
You know what else is no bueno ?
You murdered the Beast .
Yeah , well , let me call AAA for you .
I 'm sure they 'll be right over .
So you have to play your cards as ...
Whoo , that onesie was starting to cut off my circulation .
- To your vagina ? - Your vagina .
What 'll you have , Florida ?
He strikes me as the , uh , lemon drop type .
You know , something with an umbrella or something like that .
I heard " something with an umbrella . " Make it two .
Three please . Three .
So that 's your sidekick .
ALBUQUERQUE : That 's my partner .
You might look at Flagstaff and think :
" Oh , he 's a little slight , diminutive . "
Effeminate even , but he 's a real beast in battle . Yeah .
Come on . You 're being sweet . You sweet , sweet man . Thank you .
- Well , I love you . - Love you too .
Yeah , you know , Tubbs to my Crockett over here .
He may look a little bookish , but he 's an animal too .
He eats zombies for breakfast , shits them out by lunch .
Cheers .
He shits out everything by lunch .
[ METAL BANGING ]
What the hell was that ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
They must have followed you .
Oh , God , those are T-800s .
Or at the very least T-700s .
- There was no T-700 . - Yeah , T-800 's the first model .
This is great , having the two of you .
Okay . Time to nut up or shut up .
- [ COCKS GUN ] - That saying 's very 2009 .
[ LAUGHS ]
- Okay . We got this . - Ho !
You don 't send a boy to do a man 's job .
We brought them here . We 'll take care of it .
Yeah , you know what ? Have at ' em .
You have a safe word in case things go bad ?
Heh , that 's good . Come on , Flag ,
let 's show these fuckers how it 's done .
Sure . You got it , boss .
Hasta la vista , baby . Terminator 2 .
- Remember ? - ALBUQUERQUE : Ready , buddy ?
He 's so cool .
Whoo , heh , heh ! Suck these bullets !
Come on ! Get you some !
Anybody else find those two uniquely annoying ?
- ALBUQUERQUE : Get it ! - Uniquely ? No .
Well , I don 't love their chances .
They ignored rule 52 , don 't be afraid to ask for help .
FLAGSTAFF : Get fucked in the face , bitch !
- Flagstaff ? - Yeah , boss ?
You made the all-star team today . I mean , no kidding .
Unbelievable job .
And is it me , or are those Bolts
they 're just getting meaner by the day ?
- They 're full-blown dickheads . - I got an action shot of you
that 's going right into the scrapbook .
This is gonna be a good one . You just keep raising the bar ,
and that 's why we will continue to ride these highways together .
- I 'm so proud of you . - I learned from the best .
- Oh , come on now . - Nice work , Querq .
ALBUQUERQUE : Thank you . Thank you .
This is gonna be a hell of a shot . Ha , ha !
It 's so cool he let you wear the hat .
- NEVADA : Querq ? - Yeah ?
I think you got a little something here .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Oh , what , that ?
[ ALBUQUERQUE CLEARS THROAT ]
Oh , yeah , that 's just ... That 's just a tattoo .
[ ALBUQUERQUE CHUCKLES ]
Sorry , you got a tattoo of a zombie bite ?
No , it 's just a tattoo I got one night in Bernalillo .
Huh .
All right , everybody .
Just take it easy . Everything 's fine .
Nevada , why don 't you whip up some of your signature ...
[ GROANS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
All right . That was a little weird , huh ?
- Yeah . - All right . Just calm down .
We 'll just have a drink , you know .
[ GULPS HARD ]
So we can just kind of celeb ... Celeb ...
[ ALL GASPING ]
Excuse me . It 's okay .
It 's just nerves from the fight . Just ...
[ GROWLS ]
Uh , you guys , I think
Albuquerque might be infected .
Me ? I 'm infected ?
[ ALBUQUERQUE COUGHS ]
You got bit twice .
- Ah , Flagstaff ! - No , no . That 's a lie .
Trust me . Okay ? Trust me .
I don 't get bit . I never get bit .
I don 't get bit either . We 're slippery .
- See ? - I know . Are you okay ?
- I 'm fine . I 'm totally fine . - You are ?
- I 'm fine . - Okay , he 's fine . He 's fine .
No , he 's not fine . No .
No . You 're starting to look like a T-800 . Terminator 2 .
- [ GROWLING ] - [ GASPS ]
No . No , no , no !
No !
Aah !
Move ! Move ! Get out of the way .
Aah ! Aah !
Ow !
No ! No !
[ GUNFIRE ]
Flagstaff , you 're breaking
like 10 commandments right now !
This is for what you did to the Beast ! Unh !
Sorry !
[ GRUNTING ]
- How you doing ? - Bad !
- How are you ? - Bad !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Sorry , shoes . Sorry , Elvis .
[ GROANS ]
Oh , shit . Oh !
- How you doing now ? - Still bad ! You wanna switch ?
Switch ? How would that benefit me ?
[ GROANS ]
Shit !
[ YELPING ]
- Help ! Shoot him ! Shoot him ! - I don 't wanna hit you !
Shit .
Gun , gun , gun ! Oh , shit !
TALLAHASSEE : Stop shooting ! I got this !
Great , because I 'm reloading !
[ GROANING ]
[ YELLS ]
Don 't swing ! Don 't swing ! Don 't swing ! Swing !
Shit !
No , no , no , not me ! Not me ! Oh , fuck !
NEVADA : Hasta la vista , baby .
[ IMITATES ELVIS ] Thank you . Thank you very much .
- Those guys are dicks . - [ BOTH PANTING ]
TALLAHASSEE [ IN NORMAL VOICE ] : Great job .
Thank you .
- Ah . Can I wear the hat ? - Oh , negatory .
- Cool . - Zombie Kill of the Year ?
COLUMBUS : Mm , sorry . Not with the performance just turned in
by Matteo Bianchi of Pisa , Italy .
[ SPEAKING IN ITALIAN ]
[ ROARING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
COLUMBUS : Yeah , yeah . That Pisa .
COLUMBUS : Bravisimmo , Mateo .
Ahh , Sunday , Sunday , Sunday !
COLUMBUS : Jesus , Big Fat Death is right .
That thing is , like , a huge rollover risk .
It is .
Hey , dude , I think you should ask her to come with us .
- No , no , no . - Come on , yes .
I think they make a nice match .
Look , what have I been telling you guys ?
I 'm trying to shed baggage , not pick it up .
- Yeah . - Besides , she wouldn 't do that .
She 's not the type .
Stay safe , Sunshine State .
Excuse me .
Stay dangerous , Nevada .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Okay . Hey , no offense , but my sister is still out there .
Wanna hit the old road .
If by some miracle you don 't die ...
there 's always room in my driveway .
I best stay alive .
[ NEVADA CHUCKLES ]
Okay , you 're back . Good .
Do you know how to drive one of these things ?
I 'm gonna just pop that puppy off of there
and then you guys can jump in .
Nice .
She 's a big old stallion , but I can tame her .
[ GROANS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ ENGINE RUMBLES ]
[ GEAR SHIFT GRINDING ]
TALLAHASSEE : Whoo !
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
Oh , shit .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- I think he 's got the hang of it . - TALLAHASSEE : Shit !
- No . No , no . - No , no , no .
TALLAHASSEE : Goddamn motherfucker !
Got it .
[ ENGINE SPUTTERS , DIES ]
Fuck , fuck , fuck , fuck !
Maybe you should leave a note .
That 's your department .
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
I ... I just can 't do it .
Yeah . I 'll drive .
What was that ?
Satisfying .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Teamwork . Always put the team first .
I can 't believe I didn 't have that . Stupid .
You know , if Flagstaff was so great ,
then where was the undeniably gorgeous
but emotionally inaccessible Kansas City ?
I don 't know . Maybe she split
because she thought they had a random relationship .
Or maybe she was just about to come back
under the thinly veiled cover of needing guns and ammo .
Wait , what are you getting at ?
I think you 're smart enough to figure it out ...
- [ MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS ] - COLUMBUS : Oh , my God .
You gotta be kidding me .
You gotta be kidding me !
You gotta be fucking kidding me .
Why the hell is she still alive ?
Oh , my God , I literally missed you guys . Yay !
Oh , my God .
Whoa !
Just ... No , just look ahead .
Hi , old guy !
Let 's hang out .
- Ha-ha-ha ! - It is so weird to see you .
The last time I saw you , you were like a ...
- You were a zombie . - I wish .
Stupid nut allergy .
- Nut allergy ? Oh . - Yeah .
Yeah , I think it was the trail mix Wichita gave me .
Who knew there were nuts in trail mix .
MADISON : Not me . I thought it was vegan .
I kept trying to tell you
it was only an allergic reaction , but you thought
- I was trying to bite you . - Yeah , well ...
- Not that you minded last time . - Mm .
Thank you for shooting over my head .
I was really just trying to scare you off .
You 're not gonna get rid of me that easy .
- Oh , no ! - Ha-ha-ha .
There I was , hiding in the woods , when I thought :
" I used to live in a freezer , so why not a freezer on wheels ? "
Can 't argue with that logic .
I really miss this .
Was that sarcasm ?
[ WHISPERS ] Was it ?
Mm-hm .
Why wouldn 't we just move to an island ?
That 's a really good idea .
Then there wouldn 't be zombies .
- Right . - Of course .
We should go to Temptation Island .
Hey , hey , hey . Hey , hey , hey . Hey , hey .
- What ? - Hey , hey .
- Hey , hey . Hey , hey . - Hey , hey .
Just ... Just eyes on the road .
Do you want me to change the CD or anything ?
Is this a CD playing ?
- Yeah . It 's Port ... - What is this ?
It 's Portishead .
- This is Portishead ? - Yeah . You know what 's funny ?
I used to think it was called " Portashed "
until I went to one of the concerts , and she explained .
Yeah , I would think " Portasheed . "
- Right . Yeah , that 's funny . - Yeah .
COLUMBUS : It was obvious to me
that Wichita and I were meant to be together ,
which is why Madison 's return
could not have been worse timing .
Of course , I was glad she wasn 't a zombie .
But couldn 't she have just gone back to her mall fridge ?
Hey . Hey , look , look , look . Look .
[ GASPS ]
[ MUTTERS ]
Look .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
We made it to Baby-lon .
COLUMBUS : If you hear more than the usual excitement in my voice ,
it 's for two reasons .
One , we may have caught up to Little Rock ,
for real this time .
And two , we may have
finally found our forever home ,
which is what I 've been looking for all along .
- Whoa , Babylon . - I love that song .
- Hm ? - This place is soy cute .
[ MADISON GIGGLES ]
- Whoa , Jesus ! - What the fuck ?
- Enjoy the little things . - My bags were in there !
- No , they weren 't . - No guns allowed !
[ LAUGHS ]
I like this place already . You got a sense of humor .
No guns allowed .
I 'm not giving up my guns under any circumstances , period-o .
Well , then , there 's no way you 're getting up to Babylon .
You know , you could always wait in the car .
Do you wanna see Little Rock or not ?
[ SIGHS ]
- [ INDISTINCT CHATTERING ] - [ DRUMS PLAYING ]
TALLAHASSEE : There she is !
BERKELEY : I 'm on a 40-day bowel blast .
Little Rock .
- Hey . - Hi .
What are you guys doing here ?
TALLAHASSEE : I am so glad you 're safe .
- Wow , okay . - Oh , my God .
- Come here . - Hello .
Seriously , what are you doing here ?
Hey , we don 't leave each other .
I know , I know . I 'm really sorry .
Make me a pact . No more notes . Ever .
- No more notes . Ever . - Ever . Great .
Just so you know , there 's no group sex .
- Okay , fine , group sex . - Oh , whoa .
Hey , Wichita . That means you 're Columbus ,
and that makes you Tallahassee .
- Berkeley ? - You 're from Berkeley ?
- You 're Berkeley ? - No , come on .
What are the chances we 're both from Berkeley ?
- Berkeley ! - Calm down , calm down . Okay ?
Thank you for coming to check up on me , I guess .
But you have to understand these people are peaceful ,
and they 're friendly and nice .
And honestly , I don 't think you 're gonna fit in here .
- They melted our fucking weapons ! - This is exactly what I meant .
Guys , I think we should stay .
- You don 't get a vote . - I do get a vote .
Haven 't you ever heard of women suffering ?
Women 's suffrage ?
- No , honey . - Oh , boy .
- Who the hell is this ? - I 'm Madison .
- Don 't say it . - You 'll love this .
- Don 't say it . - That 's Columbus ' girlfriend .
It 's official .
Wow , you just didn 't
waste any time , did you ?
- Well , thank you for your vote . - And you 're welcome .
Okay . I 'm late for my drum circle , so I gotta go .
WOMAN : Hey , Little Rock !
Sorry about that .
[ PLAYING OFF-BEAT FOLKSY TUNE ]
COLUMBUS : Seeing Little Rock safe
and surrounded by friends her own age ,
Tallahassee realized his nest was now empty .
And he began to hear the call of the buffalo .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ PEOPLE EXCLAIMING , LAUGHING ]
MAN : All right , I 'm ready !
Come on , don 't be so Gloria Glum .
I told you guys I was leaving .
So , what , you 're just gonna split ?
It 's time . Gotta set out on my own adventures .
Little Rock 's safe ,
and , uh , a lone wolf 's gotta hunt .
So where are you gonna go ?
The direction 's the destination . West .
West is that way .
Yeah . Anyway , like the title of a great Phil Collins song :
" If You Love Somebody , Set Them Free . "
- Pretty sure that wasn 't him . - Pretty sure it was .
- No , it was someone else . - Pretty sure it was him .
Yeah . Peace .
Uh , I 'm not much for goodbyes , so ...
Just don 't say the pig thing .
Keep your tits dry .
- Oh , okay . - Didn 't see that coming , right ?
I would 've rather the pig thing .
[ CHUCKLING ]
Hey .
Hey , don 't do nothing I wouldn 't not do .
- You get what I 'm saying . - Not really , no .
No ? Okay .
[ SOBBING ]
Anyway , gonna miss you guys .
[ SUCKS TEETH ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ MADISON WAILS ]
I will never forget you , what 's-his-name .
- See you , pals . - It 's Tallahassee . I told you .
Sally Tally !
[ SOBBING ]
[ TALLAHASSEE WHISTLING " HOME ON THE RANGE " ]
TALLAHASSEE : ♪ Give me a home Where the buffalo roam ♪
♪ And the deer And the antelope play ♪
♪ Where seldom is heard A discouraging word ♪
♪ And the skies are not ... ♪
- [ LOUD THUD ] - [ TIRES SQUEAL ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLING ]
T-800s .
That decides it .
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
[ STRUMMING FOLK TUNE ]
♪ Kumbaya ♪
♪ Kumbaya , Buddha ♪
Everybody . ♪ Kumbaya ♪
MAN : Coming to you . Oh !
There it is . Let 's start again .
COLUMBUS : Oh , it 's all right . I got it .
Excuse me . Yes . I got it .
- You 're supposed to kick it back . - Really ?
- You never seen hacky sack ? - I thought it 's like hopscotch .
- Salty Taffy 's back ! - Holy shit !
Hey , T-800s , a whole swarm of them , heading right this way .
Those goddamn fireworks might as well be a dinner bell !
Stop the fireworks ! Stop the music !
Everybody shut the fuck up !
Shut up .
Question :
Did you melt all the weapons ?
Yeah , that 's how we made these peace thingies .
- Oh , Jesus . - My guns !
Hey . Hello . I got something going .
I think I might have a plan .
- Oh . - What ?
Heh , I got nothing . I 'm just a songwriter .
No . No , you 're a song transcriber .
- Listen , Berkeley ? - Yeah ?
I don 't think this is gonna work out .
Even 12-year-olds know
who Bob Dylan is , you fucking poser .
Oh , my God . I 'm not gonna lie , I have truly enjoyed
this moment , but there are zombies approaching .
Okay . Uh , Civil War general , you must know how to fight ?
Sure .
Poverty , sexism , social injustice .
- We could try running . - I 'm done running .
I mean , what good is a home if you can 't stay in it ?
- Columbus . - Yes , Thor ?
You 're gonna make me cry right now .
- No , please don 't . - Oh , my God .
Okay . I moved through it .
From where I stand , there 's only one thing we can do .
Group sex . Right ?
No . Um ...
We 'll fight them .
You 'll be the first to die , but I like your enthusiasm .
- You might die . - Thank you for your sacrifice .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
TALLAHASSEE : All right , everybody , listen up .
They outnumber us 100 times , but they ain 't got what we do .
- Guns ? - We don 't have guns .
- What ? - What we do have
is heart , brains and biodiesel .
We 're gonna light these zombies up
like it 's the Fourth of July .
Then we hit the stragglers .
What we do is we form a gauntlet .
[ YELLS ]
One , two , three , yah !
- Then we mop them up . - Sick .
- This is gonna work , right ? - It has to .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ MOANING , GROWLING ]
- Rolling . Whoa ! - Whoa , whoa !
- Keep screwing . - Yeah , I am .
- Keep screwing . - I am .
No turning back now .
LITTLE ROCK : Okay , there we go .
Nice .
Yeah . Oh , that 's gonna work .
[ WHISTLES , POPS ]
- Oh ! - Oh , that 's pretty .
That means the zombies are coming !
MADISON : The zombies are coming !
- Time to nut up or shut up . - You need a new line .
Let 's kick some dicks .
Just because it rhymes doesn 't make it a great catchphrase .
- What 's her problem ? - I don 't know .
I like it when it rhymes .
- Here we go . - COLUMBUS : Okay .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING ]
[ ALL GROWLING ]
[ ROARS ]
- Zombies , they 're coming ! - Oh , dear .
Look out , guys ! Here they come . They 're coming !
Battle stations !
Light them up !
TALLAHASSEE : Let 's go , let 's go ! Get up to safety .
[ SCREECHING ]
Here we go .
Okay now , blow !
Come on . Now would be an ideal time to blow .
- LITTLE ROCK : It 's not working . - Damn !
God !
Holy shit . It worked .
- Oh , my God . - Okay .
Okay . Here , now we mop up the stragglers .
Okay . Yeah .
[ ZOMBIES SHRIEKING , GROWLING ]
Oh , shit .
Would those be considered stragglers ?
TALLAHASSEE : Oh , boy . Here they come .
Get ready !
Kill those motherfuckers !
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Well , guys , I hate to say this .
I think this might be the end of the road .
- Come here . - I love you guys .
- I love you more . - We had a hell of a run .
Oh , my God . They 're gonna die .
[ CAR HORN BLASTS " DIXIE " ]
[ ENGINE RUMBLES ]
Oh !
Hey !
[ GROWLS ]
Sunday , Sunday , Sunday !
Thank God for rednecks !
- Need a ride ? - Oh , yeah .
- Get in . - Let 's go !
- Are y 'all strapped in yet ? - Yep . Strapping in now .
- Rule four . Got it . - You too .
I 'm not a pussy like Columbus . Nothing personal .
- Oh , God ! - Shit !
- Seatbelts are for a reason . - Yep .
I 'm feeling a little nauseous .
- Can somebody crack a window ? - Oh , no , you don 't .
TALLAHASSEE : Whoa !
- Roll down the window . - That won 't ...
If you get sick , we all get sick .
TALLAHASSEE : Woo-hoo !
Okay , okay . Oh , God .
Could you pull over so I can get eaten ?
It 'll be more comfortable .
Whoo !
- Oh , shit . Watch out ! - Do it !
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
TALLAHASSEE : Woo-hoo !
Oh , my God , you are sexy .
Can you not say " sexy " ? I 'm already nauseous .
[ ALL YELLING ]
Shit , Shit , shit ! Oh , shit .
Shit .
- Shit ! - WICHITA : You guys okay ?
Thank you for flying Big Fat Death .
Let 's go ! Let 's go ! Let 's go !
I told you these things were a rollover risk !
- NEVADA : We gotta move ! - Come on !
Hurry ! Hurry ! They 're coming !
- Oh , no ! - Come on ! Here they come !
- Go , go , go ! - Shit .
- Come on ! - Oh , shit !
TALLAHASSEE : Come on !
- Oh , shit ! - Shit !
Whoa !
- Thank you . - Thank you !
- Oh , my God ! - Yes !
Here they come !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- Go , get in . Go , go , go ! - Go , go , go !
WICHITA : Run !
[ GUNFIRE ]
- I 'm out of bullets ! - Guys , go ! I 'm right behind you !
Get in position ! Form the gauntlet ! I 'll hold them off !
Donkey Kong , motherfuckers !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
COLUMBUS : You can 't write the history of Zombieland
without telling the story of one momentous day .
The day one free man made the ultimate sacrifice
and paid respect to the Blackfoot ancestors
he may or may not have had .
The day he led the first , the last , the only
great American zombie jump .
[ YELLS ]
- [ SCREAMS ] - [ GRUNTING ]
Zombie Kill of the Year ?
COLUMBUS : Century .
Only one problem . Well , okay , two .
[ BOTH GROWLING ]
Oh !
[ TALLAHASSEE SCREAMS ]
- Hey ! - NEVADA : Tallahassee !
- Hang on , we 're coming . - LITTLE ROCK : Hold on .
- Help ! I 'm falling ! - Shit !
NEVADA : We can 't help you .
Guys ! Help me !
- Shit . What should we do ? - Throw something at them .
Oh , shit . Okay . Shit . Sorry .
Wha ... You hit me in the nuts with a hacky sack !
- Sorry . - What ?
I 'm losing my grip . I 'm gonna fall .
No ! Oh , no !
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ THUD ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ PANTING ]
[ IMITATES ELVIS ] Long live the King .
- Oh . - MADISON : Ew .
Guys ! I 'm still here !
- Give me your hand ! - WICHITA : Hold my arm .
- LITTLE ROCK : Kick your foot out . - Goddamn it , Columbus !
Point your toe !
This human chain thing is a terrible idea !
- Guh ! - WICHITA : I can 't reach .
Kick it , kick it . I got it .
Pull , pull .
Okay . I got you .
Okay .
Oh , man . Are you okay ?
- Yeah . - That was amazing .
Oh ... Thank you .
Hey .
You kept the gun ?
How could I give up my favorite Christmas present ?
Why didn 't you pull it out sooner ?
I forget about it but ... I smoked a lot of weed .
[ LAUGHS ]
Chip off the old block .
Yes .
Yes ? Oh , yes , yes ?
Yes , yes .
Yes , yes , yes ?
- Yes . Yes . - Yes ?
- Really ? - Mm-hm .
What changed your mind ?
Because Zombieland or not , we 're meant to be together .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
So basically , that means this belongs to her .
Oh , hm . Cool .
Thank you .
Okay .
[ CHUCKLES ]
- Okay . Are you ready ? - Yeah .
- Okay . I 'm good . - Okay .
- Yeah , do the damn thing . Yeah . - Okay .
- Great . Which hand do I ... ? - This one .
- Okay . - Okay , yes . Here we go .
Wow .
Come here .
[ SIGHS ]
Nicely done .
I 'm gonna walk that little spitfuck down the aisle .
It 's a good thing you didn 't die , then .
Washoe County .
- What ? - Washoe County , Nevada .
Ah , Reno .
Biggest little city in the world .
- Just go for it . - Thank you .
- Sweet . - Oh , my God .
[ GROANING ]
What ? What ?
- Oh , my gosh ! - Shit !
[ YELLS ]
[ THUDS ]
- Homer . It 's a long way down . - Our work here is done .
Let 's party !
- Come on ! - Yeah !
WICHITA : Wait for me .
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Hell , this is a 1955 Fleetwood Series 60 . Hoo !
Every hair on my body feels like a little wang .
- Yikes . - Where to ?
Mm , how about home ?
Home ?
- Yeah . - Yes , good idea .
Where 's home ?
I think we 're already there .
COLUMBUS : Because if our adventures
had taught us about anything , it was home .
Wichita didn 't need to be afraid of it .
I didn 't need to keep looking for it .
Because home isn 't a place , it 's the people you 're with .
I guess that 's why they 're called your homies .
And my homies are pretty fucking awesome .
So till next time , this is Columbus , Ohio ,
on behalf of Wichita , Little Rock ,
Reno and Tallahassee ,
saying hasta la vista , baby .
That one 's for you , Flagstaff .
[ ZOMBIE GROANS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
♪ Lord Almighty I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Higher , higher ♪
♪ It 's burning through To my soul ... ♪
COLUMBUS : Oh , hey . Yeah , sorry . One more thing .
I 'm feeling a little guilty about what Nevada said .
You know , about Murraying a certain you-know-who ?
Yeah , my bad . I blew a hole
through the finest comic actor of our generation .
But I would love to make it up to you , to all of you .
And for that , we gotta go back to 2009 .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Welcome , everyone ,
to the Garfield 3 : Flabby Tabby junket .
You 'll each have five minutes .
Please keep your questions focused on the film
and don 't go off-topic .
MURRAY : The idea of a trilogy was something ...
As an artist , you think the great ones :
Godfather and ...
uh , Lethal Weapon .
But the question is , why in the world Garfield 3 ?
- Can this be just between us ? - Yes .
Drugs cost money .
And I have to say , as an actor ,
how many of your nine lives do you think you have left ?
Well , I 've done three of these . Three Garfields .
So that 's six .
The essence of Garfield , I think ...
MURRAY : Right .
... is the hairball .
Didn 't I say ? I had a feeling this would come up .
[ SPEAKING IN SPANISH ]
You don 't wanna do the hairball really quick ?
- No . - Can you try now ?
- Give me a little hairball now ? - Come on .
[ RETCHING ]
Come on . [ GAGGING ]
[ CROAKING ]
You know , how about if I did it with you ?
- Okay . Come on . Come on . - That was close .
We 'll do a selfie together .
- [ BOTH GROANING ] - [ SHUTTER CLICKING ]
Great . Great .
[ BOTH GAGGING ]
You all right , man ?
[ GASPS ]
All over the mike .
Can we get a baby wipe for Al ?
Maybe move him back to his room ?
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Huge fan , Mr. Roker .
All right , Tim , let 's get out of here .
Somebody get my car . I 'm ready to go .
I 've never seen Roker behave that way .
That was crazy .
Sometimes it feels like you against the world .
- Oh , my God . - I think it is .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ROARS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Oh , dear .
♪ Don 't nobody worry ' bout me ♪
[ CHUCKLES ]
Excuse me ?
[ BONES CRACK ]
♪ Do what you like ♪
♪ Doing it naturally ♪
Nice !
♪ But if it 's too easy ♪
♪ They 're gonna disagree ♪
MAN : Help me !
♪ It 's your life ♪
Bill Murray ! I love some of your films . Help me !
I ain 't afraid of no ghost .
Buenas tardes , señorita .
I hate Mondays .
♪ Lord Almighty I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Higher , higher ♪
♪ It 's burning through To my soul ♪
♪ Girl , girl , girl ♪
♪ You gonna set me on fire ♪
♪ My brain is flaming ♪
♪ I don 't know Which way to go ♪
♪ And your kisses Lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light My morning sky ♪
♪ With your burning love ♪
♪ Ooh , ooh , ooh ♪
♪ I feel My temperature rising , yeah ♪
♪ Well , help me , I 'm flaming ♪
♪ I must be A hundred and nine , wow ♪
♪ Burning , burning ♪
♪ Burning And nothing can cool me , oh ♪
♪ I just might turn Into smoke ♪
♪ But I feel fine ♪
♪ Because your kisses Lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light My morning sky ♪
♪ With your burning love Yeah ♪
♪ Ah , ah , ah ♪
♪ Ah , ah , ah Burning love ♪
♪ It 's coming closer ♪
♪ The flames are now Reachin ' my body , oh ♪
♪ Please , won 't you help me ♪
♪ I feel like I 'm slippin ' away , oh ♪
♪ It 's hard to breathe ♪
♪ Oh , and my chest Is a-heaving ♪
♪ Oh , Lord have mercy ♪
♪ I 'm burning a hole where I lay ♪
♪ ' Cause your kisses Lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light My morning sky ♪
♪ With your burning love ♪
♪ Yeah , your burning love ♪
♪ Ah , your burning love ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I 'm just a hunk A hunk of burning love ♪
♪ Burning love , yeah ♪
♪ Burning love , nah ♪
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GAGGING ]
Oh , pardon . En español , it 's like :
[ HIGH-PITCHED GAGGING ]
[ WOMAN LAUGHING ]
P ... P ... Pardon my accent .